# Steve Nguyen

Taringa 4068 Brisbane QLD 0404.828.163 stevenguyen18595@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/steve-nguyen-390721225/

# **Career Objective**

A software developer with 4-year experience who has a passion in cloud-related technology and solution architecture. Strong engineering professional with a bachelor's degree focused on software development from University of Queensland. Having a good understanding of business finance and processes from a Master's degree in Finance from Queensland University of Technology.

### **Technical Skills**

- Frontend
  - Html, CSS, Bulma, Bootstrap (8/10)
  - JavaScript, Typescript (7/10)
  - ♣ Angular (7/10)
  - ♣ Vue, React (4/10)
- Backend
  - Java/Spring Boot (7/10)
  - Python/Flask (6/10)
  - C#/.Net (6/10)
  - PHP/Laravel (4/10)
  - **♣** C++
- Database
  - **♣** SQL
    - MySQL
    - PostgreSQL
    - SQLite
  - ♣ NoSQL
    - DynamoDB

- Project Management
  - Azure Dev ops
  - \rm Jira
- Code Repository
  - AWS Code Commit
  - Azure Repository
  - ♣ GitHub
- Code Editor
  - Atoms
  - ♣ Vs Code
  - Visual Studio 2019
  - 4 IntelliJ
  - Eclipse/NetBeans
  - Pydev
- **Version Control** 
  - **♣** Git
  - SourceTree

# **Education**

Professional Year May 2022 - present

Performance Education, Brisbane

Key Subjects: Australian Business Culture and Environment, Achieving Career Success, Australian Workplace Skills and Professional Business Communication

Master of Finance July 2020 – July 2021

Queensland University of Technology, Brisbane City

Bachelor of Software Engineer July 2016 - July 2019

University Of Queensland, Brisbane City

Steve Nguyen 1

# **Employment History**

#### Patient Zero Pty Ltd, Brisbane - Full Time

Jan 2022 - present

Website: https://www.pz.com.au/

As a Developer, being part of a cross functional Scrum team that delivers working software for clients that assists them solve real business problems. At Patient Zero we employ our Way of Working, created through research of best practice and hard-won experience to application development, to successfully deliver hundreds of working applications for customers.

#### **Insure Bot Pty Ltd, Brisbane - Contract**

Aug 2021 - Jan 2022

Website: https://insurebot.com.au/

As a Developer, working in a cross functional team to develop an automation project named "Insure Bot" to obtain quotes from multiple insurers and provide brokers with those quotes (moto insured quote, landlord insured quote).

#### **Freelancer**

May 2019 – Aug 2021

Develop web applications for customers who want to build small shopping websites, using Bootstrap, Bulma, Python/Flask.

# **Personal Attributes**

- ♣ Developed strong communication skills, both written and spoken throughout my career. Experience in writing reports, emails, communicating face-to-face, delivering presentations.
- Ability to work in a team from five to eight developers. Having a strong team spirit and ability to work autonomously, when required. Participated in daily/weekly meetings and was part of a values teams at Intellectual Solutions
- Able to acquire new skills quickly in other to catch up with the project if required.
- Willing to learn to sharpen personal skills to support the firm.

#### **Hobbies and Interests**

- Reading news about tech at weekend while having my favorite coffee.
- Playing badminton competitively twice a week.

## References

- Jack Marrows Founder of Insurebot Pty Ltd
  - o Email: <u>Jack@insurebot.com.au</u>
  - Linked in: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jack-marrows-5233b720/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/jack-marrows-5233b720/</a>
- Duy Tran Software Developer at Atlassian Pty Ltd
  - o Email: khanhduyth@gmail.com
  - Linked in: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/khanhduyth/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/khanhduyth/</a>
- Tung Nguyen Solution Architect at DXC Pty Ltd
  - o Email: nvttung@gmail.com
  - Linked in: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/tung-nguyen-40799011">https://www.linkedin.com/in/tung-nguyen-40799011</a>

Steve Nguyen 2